ANDREY LYAMKIN

Montreal, QC H3X2P6 | (514) 245-0605 | <u>lyamkin.andr@gmail.com</u> https://www.linkedin.com/in/andreylyamkin/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Detail-oriented Web developer with organized nature, customer-focused mindset and good critical thinking skills. Talented troubleshooter and problem solver. Familiar with code review, performance evaluation and project coordination tasks.

1+ years of professional programming experience with Java, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, PHP, HTML, CSS, ORACLE DB, MySQL DB.

6+ years of professional experience in Computer networks LAN, Wireless LAN. Advanced knowledge in TCP/IP computer networks and network security.

SKILLS

- Java, JavaScript, jQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, PHP, GitHub
- Oracle DB, SQL, PL/SQL
- Linux, CLI, TCP/IP, Routing and Switching
- Blockchain concepts

WORK HISTORY

Data center Team Leader, 01/2019 to Current

Cryptologic Inc. - Montreal, QC

- Distributed individual assignments to team members and monitored progress against production timetables.
- Held meetings with employees to evaluate performance and make plans for improvement.
- Cultivated productive and safe atmosphere while supervising team of 20 employees.

Data center Computer Maintenance Technician, 12/2017 to 01/2019

Cryptologic Inc. – Montreal, QC

- Worked with team of network engineers to rebuild whole computer data network infrastructure. It allowed increase stability, reliability and speed of the network.
- Used diagnostic tools to identify hardware failures and replace non-functional components.
- Troubleshot hardware and software to determine and rectify network problems.
- Installed equipment for data communications networks including cabling, routers, switches.

Independent Contractor, 09/2016 to 11/2017

Self-employed - Winnipeg, MB

ANDREY LYAMKIN

Montreal, QC H3X2P6 | (514) 245-0605 | <u>lyamkin.andr@gmail.com</u> https://www.linkedin.com/in/andreylyamkin/

Data center Analyst, 11/2011 to 06/2016

Cellular Network "Motiv", GSM/LTE operator – Yekaterinburg, Russia

- Collaborated with team in development of Web User interface for displaying computer network statistics. It allowed to analyze data two times faster and more efficient in compare with old approach.
- Monitored and analyzed wireless system performance, such as network traffic, security and capacity.
- Produced monthly Wireless network Health reports using advanced Excel spreadsheet functions.
- Developed database objects, including tables, views and materialized views using SQL.

Computer Network Technician, 04/2010 to 11/2011

Cellular Network "Motiv", GSM/LTE operator – Yekaterinburg, Russia

- Traveled to remote office locations to install nodes and implement client software rollouts.
- Installed equipment for data communications networks including cabling, wireless routers and telephone systems.

EDUCATION

Web and Database Programming, 05/2020

Vanier College - Montreal, QC

Java development, 09/2017

ComIT - Winnipeg, MB

Bachelor's: Information Systems and Technologies, 07/2008

Ural State Mining University – Yekaterinburg, Russia

ACTIVITIES AND INTERESTS

Literature, travel, Self-education